// var q1 = "Q 1 - Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?";
// var q2 = "Q 2 - Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?";
// var q3 = "Q 3 - Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?";
// var q4 = "Q 4 - Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?";
// var q5 = "Q 5 - Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?";
// var q6 = "Q 6 - Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?";
// var q7 = "Q 7 - Which of the following function of Array object sorts the elements of an array?";
// var q8 = "Q 8 - Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag?";
// var q9 = "Q 9 - Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?";
// var q10 = "Q 10 - Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?";


var Quiz = [{
	"question" : "Q 1 - Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
	"choices" : [ "while()","loop()","forEach()","None of above"],
	"correct_answer" : "forEach()"
},{"question" : "Q 2 - Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?",
	"choices" : ["slice()","splice()","substr()","substring()"],
	"correct_answer" : "substring()"

},{"question" : "Q 3 - Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?",
	"choices" : ["anchor()","big()","blink()","italics()"],
	"correct_answer" : "blink()"

},{"question" : "Q 4 - Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?",
	"choices" : ["concat()","join()","pop()","map()"],
	"correct_answer" : "join()"

},{"question" : "Q 5 - Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
	"choices" : ["characterAt()","getCharAt()","charAt()","None of the above"],
	"correct_answer" : "charAt()"

},{"question" : "Q 6 - Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
	"choices" : ["changeOrder(order)","reverse()","sort(order)","None of the above."],
	"correct_answer" : "reverse()"

},{"question" : "Q 7 - Which of the following function of Array object sorts the elements of an array?",
	"choices" : ["toSource()","sort()","toString()","unshift()"],
	"correct_answer" : "sort()"

},{"question" : "Q 8 - Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag?",
	"choices" : ["anchor()","big()","blink()","bold()"],
	"correct_answer" : "bold()"

},{"question" : "Q 9 - Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
	"choices" : ["toSource()","splice()","toString()","unshift()"],
	"correct_answer" : "toSourse()"

},{"question" : "Q 10 - Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?",
	"choices" : ["window.print();","B - browser.print();","navigator.print();","document.print();"],
	"correct_answer" : "window.print();"

}];

